Finding Aid for Michigan State Land Office Board records, 1816-1924
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Michigan State Land Office Board records 1816-1924
Michigan. State Land Office Board.
69 oversize folders (in 20 boxes)
101 oversize volumes
851856 Ca 2; CA Outsize
Records of United States land offices in Marquette and Grayling, Michigan. Plat and tract books containing the record of the survey and sale of public lands in Michigan.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were transferred to the Michigan Historical Collections in February 1941, from the U.S. General Land Office (later renamed the Bureau of Land Management, donor no. 6418 ) at the request of the Auditor General of Michigan.
Periodic additions to the records are not expected.
The record group is open to research.
United States land offices were the agencies responsible for the sale of the public land to individual purchasers. The first land office in Michigan was established in Detroit in 1804, although no land sales were held until 1818. As sales expanded, additional offices were established in Monroe (1823), White Pigeon (1831), Ionia (1836), Flint (1836), Sault Ste. Marie (1847), and Duncan (1854). In 1888, after several of the offices had been moved or consolidated, the state was served by four land offices, in Detroit, East Saginaw, Reed City, and Marquette. In that year, the three Lower Peninsula offices were consolidated and moved to Grayling. In 1898, the Grayling office was closed and the Marquette office became responsible for the entire state. The Marquette land office, in turn, was closed in 1925.
The records originally came from two sources. Volumes 1-51 and 78 to 87 (tract books for the Lower Peninsula) and the outsize folders (Lower Peninsula plat maps) are copies of earlier records made in 1894 for the Grayling Land Office. When that office was closed in 1898 the records were transferred to the Marquette Land Office. Volumes 52-77 and 88 (tract books for the Upper Peninsula) and volumes 150A-161 (plat maps for the Upper Peninsula) are the original records kept in the Marquette Land Office (originally in Sault Ste. Marie) beginning in 1847.
The records were transferred to the General Land Office in Washington, D.C., when the Marquette Land Office was closed in 1925. In 1940, the Auditor General of Michigan, who was the chairman of the Michigan State Land Office Board, accepted the records for the state. (The State Land Office Board was established in 1937, and was not related to the Michigan State Land Office, which was abolished in 1914 and replaced by the Public Domain Commission.) Because of crowded conditions in the State Capitol, the Auditor General asked that the records be deposited in the Michigan Historical Collections, where they could be used by a WPA Writers Project study of the disposal of public lands in Michigan. They have been on deposit at this library since that time.
Subjects:
Forests and forestry--Michigan.; Land titles--Michigan.; Land use--Michigan.; Public lands--Michigan.; Surveyors--Michigan.
Contributors:
United States. Grayling Land Office.; United States. Marquette Land Office.; United States. General Land Office.
- Tract Books
  The tract books detail the original sale by the federal government of each piece of public land in the state, beginning with the opening of the Detroit Land Office in 1818. (These volumes do not include information about lands contained in private claims.)
  The tract books for the Upper Peninsula are original records kept, beginning in 1847, by the land office in Sault Ste. Marie (in 1857 moved to Marquette). The tract books for the Lower Peninsula were copied, by hand in 1894, from an earlier record. After the earlier records were copied, some new entries were added and old entries were revised or updated. Some entries are dated as late as 1920. The tract books are arranged (in a somewhat random order) by township number, and within each township by section.
  No names of townships appear in the collection, so it will be necessary for the researcher to discover the numerical designation in terms of township and range. A brief description of townships, ranges, and other details of the U.S. land survey system can be found (as of 2007) at the web site of the National Atlas of the United States http://nationalatlas.gov/articles/boundaries/a_plss.html. The range, township, and section of a particular place can be found using maps such as those in Henry F. Walling's Atlas of the State of Michigan (Detroit: R. M. and S. T. Tackabury, 1873, 1875, or 1884); or the Mapbook of Michigan Counties (Lansing: Two Peninsula Press, 1984). Range and township numbers for Washtenaw County Townships are as follows:
  Ann Arbor R6E, T2S
  Augusta R7E, T4S
  Bridgewater R4E, T4S
  Dexter R4E, T1S
  Freedom R4E, T3S
  Lima R4E, T2S
  Lodi R5E, T3S
  Lyndon R3E, T1S
  Manchester R3E, T4S
  Northfield R6E, T1S
  Pittsfield R6E, T3S
  Salem R7E, T1S
  Saline R5E, T4S
  Scio R5E, T2S
  Sharon R3E, T3S
  Superior R7E, T2S
  Sylvan R3E, T2S
  York R6E, T4S
  Webster R5E, T1S
  Ypsilanti R7E, T3S
  Since the townships are arranged in a somewhat random order, an index to the 88 volumes by township and range has been created. It is found appended to this finding aid.
  The information contained in an individual entry includes an exact description of the land purchased, the number of acres included in the transaction, the price per acre, the total purchase price, the name of the purchaser, the date of sale, the receipt number, and the person to whom the land was patented if this was different from the name of the purchaser. Quite often the date when the land was placed on sale appears on the page.
  Indexes to the tract books by the name of the purchaser have been made. The most convenient (as of 2007) is the General Land Office Land Records web site maintained by the U.S. Bureau of Land Management: http://www.glorecords.blm.gov. Transcriptions of and indexes to tract books have been published for several counties. These can be found in the library's online catalog under the subject "Landowners Michigan ... County Indexes". Since these books were compiled from copies of tract books in other repositories, some names and locations may not correspond exactly to the library's copy. These indexes generally show the residence of each purchaser, a piece of information not included in the library's copy of the records.
  A 1942 project by Anne Case and Theodore Clark produced a card file listing the purchaser's name and county for land purchases of 640 acres or more in these 19 counties: Antrim, Berrien, Cheboygan, Crawford, Gladwin, Ingham, Ionia, Iosco, Isabella, Lenawee, Newaygo, St. Clair, and Wexford in the Lower Peninsula, and Gogebic, Keweenaw, Luce, Marquette, Menominee, and Schoolcraft in the Upper Peninsula. The card file is not part of this electronic finding aid and is only available at the Bentley Library.
  - Lower Peninsula (Townships North and Ranges East)
    - Volume 1: T1-11, R8; T7-9, R9-17
    - Volume 2: T1-12, R5; T1-11, R6-7
    - Volume 3: T1-12, R2; part of T13, R2; T1-13, R3-4; part of T12, R5; part of T13, R5
    - Volume 4: T1-17, R1; part of T13, R2; T14-17, R2-4; T15-17, R5
    - Volume 5: T12-14, R6-7; T12-16, R8; T20, R8, T10-19, R9
    - Volume 6: T10-18, R10-11
    - Volume 7: T10-19, R12; T10-15, R13
    - Volume 8: T16-19, R13; T10-19, R14; T10-12, R15
    - Volume 9: T18-20, R1-3; T13-18, R15; T10-16, R16; T10, R17
    - Volume 10: T21-26, R1; T18-20, R4-6; T18-20, R7; T21-22, R2
    - Volume 11: T23-26, R2; T21-26, R3-4; T21-23, R5
    - Volume 12: T24-26, R5; T21-26, R6-7; T22-25, R8
    - Volume 13: T14, R1-5; T27-34, R1; T13, R2-5; T9, R3 and 5; T12, R3; T5, R4; T6, R4; T15, R4-5; T10, R5; T11, R6-7; T18, R6; T19, R6-7; T26, R8; T22-26, R9
    - Volume 14: T35-38, R1; T27-38, R2; T27-30, R3
    - Volume 15: T31-37, R3; T27-36, R4; T27-30, R5
    - Volume 16: T31-36, R5; T27-35, R6; T27-32, R7
    - Volume 17: T33-34, R7; T27-34, R8; T27-33, R9; T26-27, R10; T30-31, R10
    - Volume 18: T1-6, R9; T1-6, R10; T1-4, R11
    - Volume 19: T5-6, R11; T1-6, R12-13; T2-4, R14
    - Volume 20: T6-6, R14; T2-6, R15-16; T3-6, R17
  - Lower Peninsula (Townships North and Ranges West)
    - Volume 21: T1-7, R1-2; T1-6, R3
    - Volume 22: T7, R3; T1-7, R4-5; T1-6, R6
    - Volume 23: T7, R6; T1-7, R7-8; T1-6, R9
    - Volume 24: T7, R9; T1-8, R10-11; T1-4, R12
    - Volume 25: T5-7, R12; T1-7, R13; T1-8, R14; T1-3, R15
    - Volume 26: T4-8, R15; T1-8, R16; T1, R17; part of T8, R17
    - Volume 27: T8-10, R1-5
    - Volume 28: T8-10, R6-9; T9-10, R10-11
    - Volume 29: T8-10, R12-13; R9-10, R14-16; T9-11, R17; T11, R18
    - Volume 30: T11-19, R1; T11-17, R2
    - Volume 31: T11-17, R3; T11-17, R4; T11, R5
    - Volume 32: T12-17, R5; T11-17, R6; T11-13, R7
    - Volume 33: T14-17, R7; T11-17, R8-10; T11, R11
    - Volume 34: T12-17, R11, T11-17, R12-13; T11-16, R14
    - Volume 35: T17, R14; T11-17, R15-16; T12-17, R17-18; T14-15, R19
    - Volume 36: T20-27, R1; T18-27, R2
    - Volume 37: T18-20, R3-8; T18, R9
    - Volume 38: T19-20, R9; T18-20, R10-14; T18, R15
    - Volume 39: T19-20, R15; T18-20, R16-18
    - Volume 40: T28-38, R1; T28-36, R2
    - Volume 41: T21-30, R3; T21-29, R4
    - Volume 42: T30, R4; T21-30, R5; T21-28, R6
    - Volume 43: T29-30, R6; T21-30, R7; T21-27, R8
    - Volume 44: T28-30, R8; T21-30, R9; T21-27, R10
    - Volume 45: T28-30, R10; T21-30, R11; T21-28, R12
    - Volume 46: T29-30, R12; T21-30, R13; T21-28, R14
    - Volume 47: T29-30, R14; T21-29, R15; T21-27, R16; T21-22, R17
    - Volume 48: T37-39, R2; Bois Blanc Island, Hog Island, Garden Island, Squaw Island, Big Beaver Island, Little Beaver Island, Whiskey Island, Trout Island, Gull Island, Hat Island, North and South Manitou Islands, North and South Fox Islands, Waugoshance Point
    - Volume 49: T31-39, R3-4; T31-32, R5
    - Volume 50: T33-39, R5; T31-39, R6; T31-37, R7
    - Volume 51: T31-34, R8; T31-33, R9; T32, R10, T31-32, R11; T31, R12
  - Lower Peninsula (Townships South and Ranges East)
    - Volume 78: T3-9, R1; T4-9, R5; T4-7, R6; T10, R1-5
    - Volume 79: T8-10, R6; T4-10, R7; T4-10, R8; T5-10, R9; T5-6, R10
    - Volume 80: T1-2, R1; T1-3, R2-6; T1, R7
    - Volume 81: T2-3, R7; T1-3, R8; T1-4, R9-10; T1-3, R11; T1-2, R12; T1, R13
  - Lower Peninsula (Townships South and Ranges West)
    - Volume 82: T1-10, R1; T1-7, R2
    - Volume 83: T8-10, R2; T1-10, R3-4
    - Volume 84: T1-8, R5-8; T1-4, R9
    - Volume 85: T5-8, R9; T1-8, R10-12; T1-6, R13
    - Volume 86: T7-8, R13; T1-8, R14-17; T2-3, R18
    - Volume 87: T4-8, R18-19; T6-8, R20; T7-8, R21; T8, R22
  - Upper Peninsula (Townships North and Ranges West)
    - Volume 52: T41-47, R1-2; R40-47, R3
    - Volume 53: T40-47, R4; T40-51, R5; T42-47, R6
    - Volume 54: T48-51, R6; T42-50, R7; T42-50, R8
    - Volume 55: T43-50, R9; T42-49, R10; T41-45, R11
    - Volume 56: T46-50, R11; T41-50, R12; T41-47, R13
    - Volume 57: T48-50, R13; T41-49, R14; T41-49, R15; T40-42, R16
    - Volume 58: T43-49, R16; T39-48, R17; T39-41, R18
    - Volume 59: T42-48, R18; T36-48, R19; T36-41, R20
    - Volume 60: T42-48, R20; T38-48, R21; T38-43, R22
    - Volume 61: T44-48, R22; T37-47, R23; T35-42, R24
    - Volume 62: T43-47, R24; T33-49, R25
    - Volume 63: T32-51, R26; T58, R26; T31-32, R27
    - Volume 64: T33-52, R27; T58-59, R27
    - Volume 65: T32-52, R28
    - Volume 66: T58-59, R28; T34-35, R29; T37-53, R29; T57-59, R29; T39-42, R30
    - Volume 67: T43-53, R30; T56-59, R30; T39-47, R31
    - Volume 68: T48-58, R31; T41-52, R32
    - Volume 69: T53-58, R32; T41-57, R33
    - Volume 70: T42-56, R34; T42-46, R35
    - Volume 71: T47-56, R35; T42-52, R36
    - Volume 72: T53-55, R36; T42-54, R37; T43-49, R38
    - Volume 73: T50-53, R38; T43-53, R39; T44-50, R40
    - Volume 74: T51-52, R40; T44-51, R41; T44-51, R42; T45-48, R43
    - Volume 75: T49-51, R44; T45-50, R45; T45-50, R46
    - Volume 76: T46-49, R47; T47-49, R48; T48, R49
  - Isle Royale (Townships North and Ranges West)
    - T63-65, R36; T63-65, R37, T63-64, R38; T63-64, R39; T65-67, R34; T67, R32; T66-67, R33; T65-66, R35
  - Upper Peninsula (Townships North and Ranges East)
    - Volume 77: T41-48, R1; T41-48, R2; T41-45, R3; T41-43, R4; T41, R5; T41-43, R6, T41-43, R7; T41-42, R8
  - Upper Peninsula, Supplement A
    - Volume 88: Mostly townships 42-52N and some islands
- Plat Books
  Plat books (v. 150A-161 and 69 outsize folders in Boxes 1-20): The collection originally contained 73 volumes of plat books, containing copies of the original maps produced by the U.S. land survey for all townships in Michigan, along with some original maps of later surveys of private claims and government reserves. The main series of township plats is drawn at a scale of 1:31,680 (2 inches to a mile). Some of the maps (especially those of the southern Lower Peninsula) include only section outlines, bearings, deviations, and a few landmark physical features located on section lines. Other maps (especially for the Upper Peninsula) include extensive information about physical and cultural features. As a general rule, none of these maps show land ownership. The plat books for the Lower Peninsula are lithographic copies made in 1894. The Upper Peninsula maps are hand-drawn copies, made beginning in 1847, and have extensive later annotations.
  Upper Peninsula plat books (v. 150A-161) are arranged by range number, so any township can be found easily if its numerical designation is known. The Lower Peninsula plat books (formerly v. 89-149) have been disbound, and arranged alphabetically by county in Boxes 1-20. (A few loose Upper Peninsula maps are also found in the boxes.)
  Another set of these plat maps is held by the State of Michigan, and has been made available online through the Dept. of Natural Resources General Land Office Plats web site http://www.michigan.gov/dnr/1,1607,7-153-10371_14793-31058--,00.html.
  - Lower Peninsula
    (Volumes 89-149 have been taken apart and arranged in folders by county and put into boxes; these plats are separately described.)
  - Upper Peninsula
    - Volume 150A: All ranges East
    - Volume 150B: R1-6W
    - Volume 151: R7-11W
    - Volume 152: R12-16W
    - Volume 153: R17-21W
    - Volume 154: R22-25W
    - Volume 155: R26-27W
    - Volume 156: R28-29W
    - Volume 157: R30-32W
    - Volume 158: R33-34W
    - Volume 159: R35-37W
    - Volume 160: R38-41W
    - Volume 161: R42-49W
- Plat Maps
  (formerly bound in v. 89-149; Upper Peninsula plat maps are found in v. 150A-161)
  - Lower Peninsula
    - Alcona County 1838-1846, 1854 (Box 1)
    - Allegan County 1826-1832, 1850 (Box 1)
    - Alpena County 1839-1840, 1854-1857, 1884, 1920 (Box 1)
    - Antrim County 1839-1840, 1850-1857 (Box 2)
      (see also Grand Traverse and Kalkaska for townships shared with those counties)
    - Arenac County 1822, 1831, 1837-1846, 1853 (Box 2)
    - Barry County 1826-1831, 1856, 1877, 1915, 1917 (Box 2)
    - Bay County 1822, 1831-1846, 1870 (Box 3)
      (see also Saginaw for townships shared with that county)
    - Benzie County 1838-1839, 1850-1851 (Box 3)
    - Berrien County 1828-1846 (Box 3)
    - Branch County 1825-1829, 1846 (Box 3)
    - Calhoun County 1825-1826, 1856 (Box 3)
    - Cass County 1828-1830, 1846 (Box 4)
      (includes township shared with St. Joseph)
    - Charlevoix County 1839-1856, 1888, 1921 (Box 4)
      (includes townships shared with Emmet)
    - Cheboygan County 1840-1856, 1904, 1922 (Box 4)
    - Clare County 1837-1856, 1923-1924 (Box 5)
    - Clinton County 1826-1855 (Box 5)
    - Crawford County 1836-1857 (Box 5)
    - Eaton County 1825-1827, 1855-1856 (Box 5)
    - Emmet County 1840-1841, 1922 (Box 6)
      (see also Charlevoix for townships shared with that county)
    - Genesee County 1822-1823, 1839, 1898, 1915 (Box 6)
    - Gladwin County 1831-1856, 1877 (Box 6)
    - Grand Traverse County 1836-1852, 1900-1904 (Box 6)
      (includes township shared with Antrim; see also Leelanau for township shared with that county)
    - Gratiot County 1831-1832, 1852 (Box 7)
    - Hillsdale County 1824-1837 (Box 7)
      (includes townships now part of Ohio)
    - Huron County 1834-1835, 1853 (Box 7)
    - Ingham County 1825-1827, 1856 (Box 8)
    - Ionia County 1826-1837, 1855-1856, 1875 (Box 8)
    - Iosco County 1837-1845, 1907-1921 (Box 8)
    - Isabella County 1830-1838, 1847, 1850 (Box 9)
    - Jackson County 1824-1825, 1855 (Box 9)
    - Kalamazoo County 1826-1830, 1850, 1856 (Box 9)
    - Kalkaska County 1837-1853 (Box 9)
      (includes township shared with Antrim)
    - Kent County 1830-1838, 1855-1856, 1890, 1906 (Box 10)
    - Lake County 1837-1839, 1905 (Box 10)
    - Lapeer County 1818-1834 (Box 10)
      (includes township shared with Sanilac)
    - Leelanau County 1839-1855, 1884 (Box 10)
      (includes township shared with Grand Traverse)
    - Lenawee County 1815-1824, 1837, 1896 (Box 11)
    - Livingston County 1823-1825, 1849 (Box 11)
    - Mackinac County 1827, 1844 (Box 11)
      (includes Bois Blanc Island only; see volumes for remainder of county)
    - Macomb County 1817-1818, 1836 (Box 11)
    - Manistee County 1837-1839, 1847, 1856, 1906, 1917 (Box 12)
    - Mason County 1835-1839, 1856, 1884 (Box 12)
    - Mecosta County 1837-1839, 1847, 1856, 1914 (Box 12)
    - Midland County 1831-1832, 1839, 1852 (Box 12)
    - Missaukee County 1837-1840, 1852-1856, 1909, 1912 (Box 13)
    - Monroe County 1817-1854, 1865, 1884, 1924 (Box 13)
      (includes township shared with Wayne and townships now part of Ohio)
    - Montcalm County 1831-1839, 1848, 1856, 1890, 1907, 1911 (Box 14)
    - Montmorency County 1839-1840, 1850-1857 (Box 14)
    - Muskegon County 1836-1838 (Box 14)
    - Newaygo County 1836-1838, 1856-1857, 1918 (Box 14)
    - Oakland County 1816-1818, 1823, 1868, 1915, 1917 (Box 15)
    - Oceana County 1837-1838 (Box 15)
    - Ogemaw County 1838-1839, 1845-1846, 1883, 1907 (Box 15)
    - Osceola County 1837-1839, 1847-1848, 1856 (Box 16)
    - Oscoda County 1838-1840, 1846 (Box 16)
    - Otsego County 1839-1840, 1850-1857, 1895, 1922 (Box 16)
    - Ottawa County 1831-1832, 1837-1838 (Box 16)
    - Presque Isle County 1839-1840, 1850-1857 (Box 17)
    - Roscommon County 1837-1840, 1849-1852 (Box 17)
    - Saginaw County 1821-1824, 1831-1834, 1839-1840, 1906 (Box 17)
      (includes townships shared with Bay)
    - St. Clair County 1817-1818, 1822-1824, 1834-1837, 1855-1856 (Box 18)
      [T2,R16 missing]
    - St. Joseph County 1826-1829, 1835, 1843-1845, 1895 (Box 18)
      (see also Cass for township shared with that county)
    - Sanilac County 1822-1823, 1834-1835 (Box 18)
      (missing T13, R16; see also Lapeer for township shared with that county)
    - Shiawassee County 1822-1823, 1826, 1831, 1848 (Box 19)
    - Tuscola County 1821-1822, 1834-1839, 1914 (Box 19)
    - Van Buren County 1829-1830, 1844, 1883 (Box 19)
      (missing T2, R18)
    - Washtenaw County 1816-1819, 1824-1825, 1844-1849 (Box 20)
    - Wayne County 1816-1819, 1824, 1840-1849, 1913-1920 (Box 20)
      (see also Monroe for township shared with that county)
    - Wexford County 1837-1839, 1848, 1852
Range and Township Index to Tract Books
1N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5-7E 2
8E 1
9-11E 18
12-13E 19
1-3W 21
4-6W 22
7-9W 23
10-12W 24
13-15W 25
16-17W 26
2N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5-7E 2
8E 1
9-11E 18
12-14E 19
15-16E 20
1-3W 21
4-6W 22
7-9W 23
10-12W 24
13-15W 25
16W 26
3N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5-7E 2
8E 1
9-11E 18
12-14E 19
15-17E 20
1-3W 21
4-6W 22
7-9W 23
10-12W 24
13-15W 25
16W 26
4N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5-7E 2
8E 1
9-11E 18
12-14E 19
15-17E 20
1-3W 21
4-6W 22
7-9W 23
10-12W 24
13-14W 25
15-16W 26
5N 1E 4
2-3E 3
4E 3&13
5-7E 2
8E 1
9-10E 18
11-13E 19
14-17E 20
1-3W 21
4-6W 22
7-9W 23
10-11W 24
12-14W 25
15-16W 26
6N 1E 4
2-3E 3
4E 3&13
5-7E 2
8E 1
9-10E 18
11-13E 19
14-17E 20
1-3W 21
4-6W 22
7-9W 23
10-11W 24
12-14W 25
15-16W 26
7N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5-7E 2
8-17E 1
1-2W 21
3-5W 22
6-8W 23
9-11W 24
12-14W 25
15-16W 26
8N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5-7E 2
8-17E 1
1-5W 27
6-9W 28
10-11W 24
12-13W 29
14W 25
15-17W 26
9N 1E. 4
2E 3
3E 3&13
4E 3
5-7E 2
8-17E 1
1-5W 27
6-11W 28
12-17W 29
10N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5E 2&13
6-7E 2
8E 1
9E 5
10-11E 6
12-13E 7
14-15E 8
16-17E 9
1-5W 27
6-11W 28
12-17W 29
11N 1E 4
2-4E 3
5E 2
6-7E 2&13
8E 1
9E 5
10-11E 6
12-13E 7
14-15E 8
16E 9
1-2W 30
3-5W 31
6-7W 32
8-11W 33
12-14W 34
15-16W 35
17-18W 29
12N 1E 4
2E 3
3E 3&13
4E 3
5E 2&3
6-9E 5
10-11E 6
12-13E 7
14-15E 8
16E 9
1-2W 30
3-4W 31
5-7W 32
8-10W 33
11-14W 34
15-18W 35
13N 1E 4
2E 3,4&13
3-5E 3&13
6-9E 5
10-11E 6
12-13E 7
14E 8
15-16E 9
1-2W 30
3-4W 31
5-7W 32
8-10W 33
11-14W 34
15-18W 35
14N 1-4E 4&13
5E 13
6-9E 5
10-11E 6
12-13E 7
14E 8
15-16E 9
1-2W 30
3-4W 31
5-6W 32
7-10W 33
11-14W 34
15-19W 35
15N 1-3E 4
4-5E 4&13
8-9E 5
10-11E 6
12-13E 7
14E 8
15-16E 9
1-2W 30
3-4W 31
5-6W 32
7-10W 33
11-14W 34
15-19W 35
16N 1-5E 4
8-9E 5
10-11E 6
12E 7
13-14E 8
15-16E 9
1-2W 30
3-4W 31
5-6W 32
7-10W 33
11-14W 34
15-18W 35
17N 1-5E 4
9E 5
10-11E 6
12E 7
13-14E 8
15E 9
1-2W 30
3-4W 31
5-6W 32
7-10W 33
11-13W 34
14-18W 35
18N 1-3E 9
4-5E 10
6E 10&13
7E 10
9E 5
10-11E 6
12E 7
13-14E 8
15E 9
1W 30
2W 36
3-9W 37
10-15W 38
16-18W 39
19N 1-3E 9
4-5E 10
6-7E 10&13
9E 5
12E 7
13-14E 8
1W 30
2W 36
3-8W 37
9-14W 38
15-18W 39
20N 1-3E 9
4-7E 10
8E 5
1-2W 36
3-8W 37
9-14W 38
15-18W 39
21N 1-2E 10
3- 5E 11
6-7E 12
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-17W 47
22N 1-2E 10
3-5E 11
6-8E 12
9E 13
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-17W 47
23N IE 10
2-5E 11
6-8E 12
9E 13
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-16W 47
24N 1E 10
2-4E 11
5-8E 12
9E 13
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-16W 47
25N 1E 10
2-4E 11
5-8E 12
9E 13
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-16W 47
26N 1E 10
2-4E 11
5-7E 12
8-9E 13
10E 17
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-16W 47
27N 1E 13
2-3E 14
4-5E 15
6-7E 16
8-10E 17
1-2W 36
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7-8W 43
9-10W 44
11-12W 45
13-14W 46
15-16W 47
28N 1E 13
2-3E .14
4-5E 15
6-7E 16
8-9E 17
1-2W 40
3-4W 41
5-6W 42
7W 43
8-9W 44
10-12W 45
13-14W 46
15W 47
29N 1E 13
2-3E 14
4-5E 15
6-7E 16
8-9E 17
1-2W 40
3-4W 41
5W 42
6-7W 43
8-9W 44
10-11W 45
12-13W 46
14-15W 47
30N 1E 13
2-3E 14
4-5E 15
6-7E 16
8-10E 17
1-2W 40
3W 41
4-5W 42
6-7W 43
8-9W 44
10-11W 45
12-13W 46
14W 47
31N 1E 13
2E 14
3-4E 15
5-7E 16
8-10E 17
1-2W 40
3-5W 49
6-7W 50
8-9W 51
11-12W 51
27W 63
32N 1E 13
2E 14
3-4E 15
5-7E 16
8-9E 17
1-2W 40
3-5W 49
6-7W 50
8-11W 51
26-27W 63
28W 65
33N 1E 13
2E 14
3-4E 15
5-6E 16
7-9E 17
1-2W 40
3-4W 49
5-7W 50
8-9W 51
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
34N 1E 13
2E 14
3-4E 15
5-6E 16
7-8E 17
1-2W 40
3-4W 49
5-7W 50
8W 51
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
35N 1-2E 14
3-4E 15
5-6E 16
1-2W 40
3-4W 49
5-7W 50
24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
36N 1-2E 14
3-4E 15
5-E 16
1-2W 40
3-4W 49
5-7W 50
19-20W 59
24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
37N 1-2E 14
3E 15
1W 40
2W 48
3-4W 49
5-7W 50
19-20W 59
23-24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
38N 1-2E 14
3E 15
1W 40
2W 48
3-4W 49
5-6W 50
19-20W 59
21-22W 60
23-24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29W 66
39N No E None
2W 48
3-4W 49
5-6W 50
17-18W 58
19-20W 59
21-22W 60
23-24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29-30W 66
31W 67
40N No E None
3W 52
4-5W 53
16W 57
17-18W 58
19-20W 59
21-22W 60
23-24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29-30W 66
31W 67
41N 1-8E 77
1-3W 52
4-5W 53
11W 55
12-13W 56
14-16W 57
17-18W 58
19-20W 59
21-22W 60
23-24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29-30W 66
31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
42N supplement 88
1-8E 77
1-3W 52
4-6W 53
7-8W 54
10-11W 55
12-13W 56
14-16W 57
17W 58
18-19W 59
20-22W 60
23-24W 61
25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65
29-30W 66
31W 67
32W 68
33W 69
34-35W 70
36W 71
37W 72
43N supplement 88
1-7E 77
1-3W 52
4-6W 53
7-8W 54
9-11W 55
12-13W 56
14-15W 57
16-17W 58
18-19W 59
20-22W 60
23W 61
24-25W 62
26W 63
27W 64
28W 65